articlesender.com 2007-12-15

# Article Submission

  System Status: Live 

REGISTERED USERS

MAIN SERVICES

OTHER SERVICES

TESTIMONIAL

WOW! What a great service! I have used many submission sites, but this exceeds my expectation by miles. What a great service and submission speed is awesome. Keep It Up! 

Peter Nisbet   

TESTIMONIAL

Again, I have to thank you on how easy it is to get my articles out onto the web. I'm done in 10 minutes rather than 10 hours. I have more time for myself and to spend with family. 

Dr. Melanie Beingessner   

TESTIMONIAL

I have to say that I am a bit biased being one of the owners brother, but this service kicks ass! 

Chris D   

TESTIMONIAL

ArticleSender provides an amazing article distribution service with fast support and incredible delivery times. The responses I get every time I use ArticleSender are nothing short of wonderful. Keep up the good work folks! 

Mike Rogne   

  Read All Testimonials

|    

## The Article Distribution Center Privacy Policy

In general, articlesender.com does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information except in very specific instances, such as, for example, when you enroll as an advertiser in the Services, as defined below. Whenever we collect such information, you will have a choice regarding whether to provide it, how it will be used, and to whom it will be disclosed. The instances in which articlesender.com does collect and use information are specifically described in this Privacy Policy.

articlesender.com provides easy to use services, including The Article Distribution Center Search (located at www.articlesender.com)(the "Services"). The Services are made available by articlesender.com and, its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively "articlesender.com"). articlesender.com values its users and their concerns about privacy. To this end, articlesender.com engages in consistent information practices and uses its best efforts to make clear disclosures regarding those practices. This Privacy Policy is a part of that effort.

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by articlesender.com. If there are any exceptions, we will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information.

Please be aware that, as part of the Services, articlesender.com provides links to Web sites operated by third parties, and also provides search results and similar services to third parties for display on their own Web sites or applications. articlesender.com is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications. Also, please be aware that banner ads on articlesender.com are provided by a third party, which may collect cookies as part of the process of serving those ads. These cookies are typically used for the purpose of tracking performance of the banner ads. articlesender.com does not determine which information will be collected by that third party. Please see the paragraph below regarding Third Party Banner Ads.

**What information does articlesender.com collect and how is it used? Does articlesender.com disclose information to third parties?**  
articlesender.com may collect any or all of the following three types of information: (a) traffic or clickstream data, (b) cookies, or (c) contact information and other personally identifying information. articlesender.com's collection and use of each type of data is described below, as well as the ways (if any) in which the data may be shared with third parties.

(a) Traffic or Clickstream Data. Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. articlesender.com may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our Web site, or searched Web sites for the term "fly fishing." articlesender.com collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) users access. For example, articlesender.com's servers collect information about the site from which you entered to enable articlesender.com to calculate and pay its affiliates, information about the most frequently searched terms to help its advertisers provide the most relevant search results, information about usage to check for fraudulent behavior or other abnormalities and to ensure that our Services are technically superior. In addition to the foregoing applications, articlesender.com uses the information (in aggregate form) to better design the Services.

(b) Cookies. Like many sites, articlesender.com collects information about online behavior using cookies. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning, as well as to streamline their experiences using the Services. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies lets us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. articlesender.com may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. To articlesender.com, using information within cookies is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. articlesender.com may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

(c) Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information. articlesender.com can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become an advertiser with articlesender.com, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from articlesender.com and provide your name or return contact information, or (2) in connection with special offers or contests.

Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or clickstream data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request.

Finally, you may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. articlesender.com uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. Finally, from time to time, but only with your permission, articlesender.com may provide certain of its users' registration information to selected third parties who wish to participate in special promotions offered in conjunction with articlesender.com. Users may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by contacting articlesender.com.

**Is data stored by articlesender.com secure?**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, articlesender.com has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to articlesender.com (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that articlesender.com will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

**Does articlesender.com collect personally identifying information from or about children?**  
articlesender.com uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any portions of the Services that require registration.

Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

**How can I access or correct any personally identifying information about me?**  
To request a copy of the personally identifiable information you have sent to articlesender.com, please send an e-mail containing your request to info@articlesender.com. You must provide your full name and the e-mail from which the request is received (and to which the response will be sent) must match the e-mail on file with articlesender.com. You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the e-mail.

**How do I find out more about articlesender.com's information practices?**  
If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact articlesender.com as follows:

**Business Affairs  
The Article Distribution Center  
E-Mail info@articlesender.com**

You may also use the above contact information if you think any information about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or if you want to change the sort of information about you that articlesender.com may have collected.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on November 22, 2005. 

* * *

Orlando, Fl: My brother, Chris Dupre has been a professional guitarist for 18 years and has been teaching guitar lessons for the past 5 years. He is taking new students for one to one lessons in your home. If you are interested, please see his [Orlando Guitar Lessons](http://www.guitar-lesson-world.com/) website.

Our Microsoft certified partner is Evision Systems for [great plains accounting](http://www.evisionsys.com/)  

| 

January 30, 2020    

ARTICLE CATEGORIES
